But
At a first read
Maybe it can be difficult to detect those emotions?
But that is why I want you to notice,
Thus, sense what is happening.
The people I write about
Don't know what they feel.
There is a kind of break or wait, perhaps a longing to reach it
you feel.
to be called minimalist.
But
If you say ...
If you turn it around, you could say it's very ...
There are prose that wastes a lot with the words and you don't.
You are very frugal with the words.
That you are a perfectionist is very clear,
There is not a single word that is there
By chance, you get a feeling when you read your books.
It may sound a little scary!
It may be a little dead about
Every word, you can almost get anxiety if you are to read something you imagine has meaning and meaning in everything.
And that is not the meaning
That it should be so.
And it is true that I do not perceive myself as a minimalist.
I have never understood how to
Write minimalist books.
Cardboard boxes,
Classes and bags.
All the time any of us said:
How much luck can you have?
The apartment was one with a balcony.
In the plant road we had a yuccapalm, a homecoming,
a cactus,
A Benjamin Fikus.
The homemade grew in half a coconut,
A farewell gift from Bob's little brother.
The inventory consisted of a flap table with chairs,
One and forty-bed.
Agency and floor lamp and more.
Nothing to the walls,
Bob thought about hanging up a towel,
With braid patterns of tapestry character.
Screw legs
on
Table and mediates on bed.
But we left everything in a single mess and went out and sat in the late afternoon sun.
We sat on the same chair.
Bob saw maybe a tern,
The women's house is just behind.
He put his beer on the back of the hand,
grabbed it in time.
The balcony echoed,
Then I thought,
the first ........
Should you be able to read
from the front and when the book ends you should recognize them, they are just back and front
They would correspond to Bob's name.
Bob.
So I thought that in the book's half first part everything should go well,
And in the other half, everything bad.
As a rorschachtest,
They do not interfere with an absolutely obvious way but they do.
You feel it.
One notices it quite
Clearly when man
Have read both.
But start by telling us who Bob?
Bob is a young man from the countryside,
raised on a farm,
that moves with its dearest to Copenhagen
Because she should study.
And he should nothing.
That's the novel.
He tries to get his life ... He tries to find out what to do.
Wandering around on the streets of Copenhagen
are friendly,
He looks very good,
It's positive vibes around him,
He is a kind of ladies' friend.
But he is very faithful to his girlfriend,
which gradually takes more and more distance from him.
I think of him like ...
Now I have to say one thing about “they”
In “they” is bob
Which gradually becomes more difficult and harder for him.
He is becoming more and more entangled.
His surrounding existence ends up eventually
Like a snare that is tightened.
Both as with that
one understands that this relationship is about to go to the forest but also because
all his situation becomes
More and more crowded.
Yes it does.
He gets depressed after all
Because he doesn't have ...
Yes, because ...?
Why?
Because he longs for something he can't get.
At first, the daughter does not know, the mother says nothing, but
Gradually she understands that too.
But
somehow so ...
their lives as well as continues ... somehow ...
Despite the knowledge of all this, they just keep living.
After a while you understand
to
The woman with whom Bob lives together is
the main character in “those”
I was very touched by "they" because, as I told you before, that I
was very reminded
My own last time with my mom when she was sick.
I think there are many like ...
you said there are many who have
related just to this and heard of this
So often when readers come to me
and said they recognize the book
So it is very often that,
it is about.
If you feel that you should lose someone, you can feel a great closeness by talking about ...
There was someone who told me,
When my brother would die
was the only thing we talked about
Where did Mom bought her bread,
I have often quoted her
In my books.
It was a great joy for her
when she was quoted.
Once it was a quote included in a review.
It was so amazing for her to
she walked around all of her village
And be proud of it.
Yes,
So something that just goes on.
Then I got started again.
And I wanted to let Bob become the main character
It was that with "the good helper"
I wanted to expand his character.
So it happened to
the young daughter from
"The",
After her mother dies,
is her family.
It felt I was good
to treat too.
Grief to lose both
The family and their hubby.
But you still had a ...
you let it still just glimpse in
"Bob" that it is related to this?
It is not an obvious continuation?
No, to me it was so obvious!
But I wanted it to stand on the back of "Bob", a continuation of "They",
one should lose what you come from,
One should find your own way,
its own form.
And it is also often one
impending break -ups of some kind that is just expected.
As
the death of the mother or
Bob and his girlfriend's separation.
You are constantly facing,
there is a break up somewhere there but one is in
Some kind
readers, especially in Denmark
who say they get furious at especially my women
because,
also the men,
they want to give them a kick or a scolding and say, get an outbreak, move, make money
do something!
I write best about those who haven't done anything yet.
Thus those who are there
The road should be selected.
Maybe because it holds so much more
than to write about someone who just goes the right path.
The most exciting thing in life is when one
Don't know the road to go.
That is incredibly simple idea that for me
And that directionlessness
Maybe reflect in the books.
We have to talk a little more about these female characters.
Now Bob is a bit like that
Figure too!
He is actually a man.
But they are often called for,
I scissors a few words from different reviews.
They are paralyzed,
evicted, jagged,
apathetic and passive.
But
Is they really?
There is a great benevolence
and an absolute lack of,
on communication indeed, in a way.
Another thing that you are also very, very busy with is details.
There is also a kind of meaninglessness there.
You can stay
you very much at
A broken saucepan handle or a dishcloth hanging in a certain way.
There are a lot of those here
The attributes around as
Maybe that's why I would like to
Challenge the form
Because I can't get away from my own voice.
So it may be.
Can you feel the prisoner in your own like ...?
If I understand you right, it's so I remove a scene, because I think
That it likes me too much.
I don't want that again.
In the same way, for example, there are words ...
I discovered when I wrote "Bob"
that I had used the word “half”
Far too many times.
Half,
as in a half apple or half a glass of water.
So
I looked through all
and many were,
At half past one
It has taken me many years to understand.
One can blast scene after scene
And it doesn't have to be difficult.
There is also in your very associative prose, which is quite close to poetry sometimes, you
Have written poetry too, right?
Yes, but very little!
That was before I debuted
I could not control my poet self
I became very sentimental.
I am constantly struggling with, not to cross that limit
I would like to reach almost to that limit
But when did you feel in prose that it had
Found, maybe you still don't feel that you had found your voice?
Here's how I can tell you, this is how I want to tell you!
The latest novels are not minimalist
Because there is
A new kind of ...
There are some shorter episodes that are more poetic
that is highly associative
Yes
And it is so exciting because,
for example
Could it be a section in "Bob"
where I want to ...
It may be so calculating to write novels
That you have to introduce something for the reader to understand that ....
so should I have a sentence that is "it happened in December"
What is it called in Swedish?
It happened in December
I was just going to ask, what are you working on right now and is it something like ...
I can say that because I am in Sweden
Because it's secret but ... can I?
I work with that several people from “those”
gets their own voices
But still it is the same daughter who is the narrator
You're left in this one,
In this group?
I wish an extended “de”